https://americanhelicopter.museum/privacy-statement/

Donate
Search for:
Privacy Statement
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by American Helicopter Museum & Education Center. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by American Helicopter Museum & Education Center for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through American Helicopter Museum & Education Center public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: American Helicopter Museum & Education Center does not read any of your private online communications.
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from American Helicopter Museum & Education Center so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center and American Helicopter Museum & Education Center family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center collects and uses your personal information to operate the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web site and deliver the services you have requested. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from American Helicopter Museum & Education Center and its affiliates. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, American Helicopter Museum & Education Center may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to American Helicopter Museum & Education Center, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within American Helicopter Museum & Education Center, in order to determine what American Helicopter Museum & Education Center services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within American Helicopter Museum & Education Center to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on American Helicopter Museum & Education Center or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of American Helicopter Museum & Education Center; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of American Helicopter Museum & Education Center, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize American Helicopter Museum & Education Center pages, or register with American Helicopter Museum & Education Center site or services, a cookie helps American Helicopter Museum & Education Center to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same American Helicopter Museum & Education Center Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the American Helicopter Museum & Education Center services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. American Helicopter Museum & Education Center encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how American Helicopter Museum & Education Center is protecting your information.
Contact Information
American Helicopter Museum & Education Center welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that American Helicopter Museum & Education Center has not adhered to this Statement, please contact American Helicopter Museum & Education Center at info@helicoptermuseum.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Museum OpenThe Museum is currently CLOSED per COVID-19 mitigation measures released by the Governor on 12/10/20. Any updates will be posted here and on Facebook.
HoursCLOSED THROUGH 1/4.
When open, hours are:
Friday - Sunday:
12pm - 5pm
Last admission:
4:30pm
Weather Closings
AHMEC adheres to West Chester Area School District closing directives as posted on its website and announced by local media. Call in advance, particularly on Sundays, to check our open status.
Get Involved
Make a Donation
Membership
Volunteer
Contact Info
1220 American Boulevard
West Chester, PA 19380
info@americanhelicopter.museum
